<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AOU Server</string>
    <string name="available_devices_string">Available Devices</string>
    <string name="paired_devices_string">Paired Devices</string>
    <string name="no_heart_beat_text">No input value</string>
    <string name="paragraph">Product Library Fire suppression systems for server rooms
	    and data centres:\n\n\nMethod 1 - Inert gas fire suppression systems for server room and Data Centres - Reduce Oxygen
        This method uses Argon/Nitrogen and sometimes a small element of CO2 to displace the oxygen in the server room.
        The basis of this method is to reduce the oxygen level to below 15%.  By reducing oxygen to this level it will suppress a fire.\n\n\n
        Method 2 - Chemical/Synthetic gas fire suppression systems for server room and Data Centres - based on cooling
    Most Chemical/Synthetic fire suppression agents have some form of cooling mechanism. These systems generally use
        less gas and do not significantly reduce oxygen levels.  However, as any synthetic or chemical agent, high doses can
        be toxic, therefor correct designs are absolutely necessary.\n\n\n

2-High humidity:\n\n

1.    Reducing the supply of fresh air to the computer room with the minimum pressurization and ventilation.\n
2.    Measure the temperature of air entering the IT equipment.\n
3.    Resolve each hot spot (which affects the air going into other IT equipment) plates with bleach, floor gratings moving, removing the \n

4.To de-humidify, the dew point must be below 15 ° C / 59 ° F (for temperatures, air-supplied IT equipment from 23 ° C / 74.4 ° F and 27 ° C / 80.6 ° F).
        Since in most refrigeration systems the dew point of the device (ADP) \n
5.    PERIODICALLY, you should monitor the temperature of dry bulb and dew point of incoming air to the IT equipment.\n\n\n

3-smoke :\n\n
1-Check local air quality reports. \n
2-Consult local visibility guides.\n
3-Keep indoor air as clean as possible .\n
4- Avoid activities that increase indoor pollution.\n
</string>
</resources>
